<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Using SFM for Vortex on vortex-sfm</title><link>/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Using SFM for Vortex on vortex-sfm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install Modes</title><link>/usage/install-modes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/usage/install-modes/</guid><description>Before you get to installing your favourite mod files, there&amp;rsquo;s one more thing you should know about: install modes.
Install modes were introduced in 0.1.0 and allow you to control how and where mods are installed and how they interact with SFM.
Merged mode Merged mode is the default install mode for new mods and will install your mods merged into a single vortex folder in your SFM directory, so SFM will see them as one mod with a lot of assets.</description></item><item><title>Installing Mods</title><link>/usage/installing-mods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/usage/installing-mods/</guid><description>Now that Vortex is fully set up, download any mods you want to install. Mod files should be the original mod archive files (*.rar, *.zip, *.7z etc).
Open the Mods screen from the Vortex sidebar and drag-and-drop the archive files into Vortex to add them to your list. You will then need to install them and enable them as per the usual Vortex installation process.
Once you Enable a mod, its files will be installed into SFM’s install directly automatically.</description></item><item><title>Search Paths</title><link>/usage/search-paths/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/usage/search-paths/</guid><description>As with any mod installed for SFM, whether manually or using SFM for Vortex, you will need to tell SFM about your new mod. You can do this manually or try the experimental auto-update.
Manual Method You need to enable the search paths for Vortex mods just like you would any other mod you have installed. Open the SFM SDK, by clicking Launch in your Steam library and selecting “Launch SDK” when prompted.</description></item></channel></rss>