<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation on vortex-sfm</title><link>/installation/</link><description>Recent content in Installation on vortex-sfm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automated Installation</title><link>/installation/automatic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installation/automatic/</guid><description>This is the easiest way to get started and you should only install manually if this doesn't work! Open up Vortex, and open the Extensions panel from the left sidebar. Click Find more to open the list of Extensions Find SFM Support and click Install Wait for the extension to install and restart Vortex when prompted. Once Vortex has restarted, just click the Manage button on Source Filmmaker (SFM) in your Games screen and you&amp;rsquo;re ready to install some mods!</description></item><item><title>Install from Archive</title><link>/installation/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installation/archive/</guid><description>If Vortex fails to install the extension for some reason, you can also download and install an archive of the extension files.
Downloading from Nexus Mods To download the extension files, click the Manual Download on the Mod page on Nexus Mods to download the archive.
Downloading from GitHub Download the latest files from the GitHub Releases page. You can also download the latest CI builds from Actions, but these are rebuilt on each commit and may not be as stable as those available on Nexus Mods.</description></item><item><title>Manual</title><link>/installation/manual/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installation/manual/</guid><description>Only attempt this if you absolutely have to. It becomes much harder to debug and much harder to upgrade. If you don’t want to enable Advanced Mode for Vortex or want to install the extension yourself, you will have to install the extension files manually. Make sure you close Vortex before proceeding.
First, unpack the archive to somewhere convenient. You should have a directory named game-sourcefilmmaker with three files inside:</description></item></channel></rss>